<resources>

    <!-- MainActivity -->
    <string name="text_view">
        Press Home button to use Your phone or Power button to turn off your screen -
        flashlight will continue to give a light.
        \nTo turn off the flashlight you need to press Back button from the application.
    </string>

    <!-- For Alert Dialogs -->

    <!-- Privacy Policy -->

    <string name="privacy_policy_button">Privacy policy</string>

    <string name="privacy_policy" translatable="false">
        \nAll the information what app able to give - is standard info for GooglePlay
        services: about phone model, about operating system version, country, ect. That info is
        the same for any app in GooglePlay. One-Tap Flashlight app not collect, use or sell any
        private information about phone owner. And this app, as it is, specially not collect any
        information at all. The app - is just a flashlight for phone. The only one task of the
        app - is to, being  small and simple, give to your phone functionality of flashlight.
        \n
        \nPermission for camera is needed just for app be able to turn on camera flash, which is
        using as flashlight.
        \n
        \nIf you have any questions about app-s Privacy Policy (the same as about the app at all)
        you can write to me on my email: pazukdev@gmail.com
        \n
        \nPazukDev
    </string>

    <!-- App Start Error -->
    <string name="app_start_error_title">Application start error</string>
    <string name="app_start_error_message">
        Camera and flashlight are missing on your device or are not responding.
        Application will be closed.
    </string>

    <!-- Camera Start Error -->
    <string name="camera_start_error_title">Camera start error</string>
    <string name="camera_statr_error_message">
        Starting and getting parameters of camera failure. Camera is not responding.
        Application will be closed.
    </string>

    <!-- Alert Dialog OnCancel Toast Text -->
    <string name="alertdialog_oncancel_toast_text">
        You can\'t cancel the dialog with button Back.
    </string>

    <!-- Buttons -->
    <!-- <string name="ok" translatable="false">OK</string> -->
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="close_app">Close application</string>






</resources>
